cbmw.org 2006-06-21

# CBMW Site Information - Privacy Policy and Copyright Information

Privacy Policay   |   Site Information   |   Copyright Information   |   Contact Us

  Welcome to the website of the Council on Biblical Manhood and Womanhood (CBMW). The following information is designed to allow you to understand our information gathering practices and to assure you of our commitment to your privacy. If you have any questions that are not answered here, please e-mail [ webmaster@cbmw.org](mailto:webmaster@cbmw.org).

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

  Before we go into detail about our privacy policy, let us make a promise to you:   
**The information you provide or that is collected by CBMW will _never_ be shared with any third party organization without your expressed permission. **

**COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

  While visiting our site, CBMW will not collect any personal information without your knowledge. There are parts of our site that require personal information, such as making purchases from our store, contacting us, requesting our free gifts, subscribing to the Journal, or joining our mailing lists. The only information we collect in these areas is the information that you provide. Your participation in providing this information is completely optional (please see below for how we use the information that you chose to provide). Apart from these areas, no personal information is collected about you. 

The personal information we collect is only the information that you specifically provide to us. We do not associate this personal information with your particular visit (i.e. we do not know what pages you looked at, what site you came from, etc…). The information you provide will be sent to our office staff but it will never be used to identify you on this or subsequent visits to our web site.

When you provide personal information, we will use it to fulfill the expectation presented on the page in which you provided it. For example, personal information provided in our store will be used to correctly bill you for your order and ship the products to you. Personal information provided in our contact and feedback areas will be used to properly respond to your request or comments. _Personal information collected from requesting the free gift on the site, subscribing to the Journal, adding yourself to our mailing list, and making purchases from our store may be used to add you to our client database and mailing list._ If you prefer not to be in our database or on our mailing list, either do not participate in providing your information on these pages or opt out by contacting our administrative offices at 1-888-560-8210.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF TECHNICAL INFORMATION**

  Some technical information is collected by our servers when you visit our site. **The technical information collected is never associated with your identity or with any personal information that you chose to provide.** Examples of technical information that may be collected include your IP address, where you came from when visiting our site, how long you stayed at CBMW, what pages you viewed while you were here, and what browser you were using. Again, this information is only seen in log files and is never associated with any personal information. It is used to help us diagnose problems on our site, see what areas are most frequently visited, and to find ways to enhance your browsing experience. 

**COOKIES**

  Cookies are small, plain-text files that are written to your computer’s hard drive. They are often used to personalize or enhance your browsing experience or to identify you to a web site (such as through remembering your username or password). **Because of our concern for your privacy, we do _not_ utilize cookies apart from the shopping carts of our on-line store, journal subscription form, and on-line donation form.** Cookies are only used in our store in order to track your shopping cart so that your order may be accurately associated with you and processed. After completing your order, these cookies expire. The cookies used in our on-line store are never seen by our servers outside of the store area (i.e. they are never used to see what other parts of our site you visit, etc…). If you prefer to avoid cookies, you may disable them in your browser settings. 

**LINKS**

  The CBMW web site contains links to other web sites. These links are provided for your benefit and do _not_ represent an endorsement or approval by CBMW of the site’s content or message or of the organization or people behind that organization or site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

**SECURITY**

  General correspondence sent through the CBMW web pages (such as sending e-mails or comments to us through our on-line forms) is not secure unless specifically noted. Do not send sensitive information through these means. It could _potentially_ be viewed by a third party while in transit.

**Our on-line store and all other areas on our site used to make purchases or donations are secure.** We use industry standard SSL connections (provided by a large and well-respected Internet hosting company) for the transmission of payment and billing information. This ensures that the information you provide is encrypted and unable to be viewed by third parties while being transmitted.

All information and materials found throughout this site are protected under copyright laws. As with printed information, none of the text, images, audio, video, or other information on this site may be copied or reproduced in any way without the expressed, written permission of CBMW. Violations of copyright laws are prosecutable.

Copyrighted information included on this site (such as some of the full-text books provided) have been used by permission. 

For questions concerning copyright and our web site or to report a potential copyright infringement of our material, please e-mail [webmaster@cbmw.org](mailto:webmaster@cbmw.org) or see below for additional contact options.

Thank you for visiting the web site for the Council on Biblical Manhood and Womanhood. We work hard to provide helpful resources for you on-line along with a pleasant browsing experience.

If you have questions about our site or if you have ideas on how we can better serve you through this site, please let us know. The easiest way to provide your comments, questions, or other feedback about the site is to send it to [webmaster@cbmw.org](mailto:webmaster@cbmw.org) You may also send it via mail to: 

> The Council on Biblical Manhood and Womanhood  
>  ATTN: Web Design Team  
>  2825 Lexington Road Box 926  
>  Louisville, KY 40280
